Contact

deannastew@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/deannastewart-msn-rn-bc-ccrn-78b84152 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

ACLS

Nursing

Certifications

ACLS

Medical-Surgical Nursing Certification

Registered Nurse

Critical Care Registered Nurse (Adult) (CCRN-A)

Deanna Stewart, MSN, RN-BC, CCRN

Registered Nurse at Harris Health System

Houston, Texas

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Hospitality Industry, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Team Building, and Healthcare. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's Degree focused in MSN - Nursing Administration and Leadership from The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth).

Experience

Harris Health System
Registered Nurse
June 2018 - Present (2 years)
Houston, Texas Area

LYNDON B. JOHNSON HOSPITAL

Specialty Area: IMU/Medical/Surgical/Telemetry

Houston Northwest Medical Center Registered Nurse March 2016 - June 2018 (2 years 4 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Specialty Area: Medical ICU

Specialty Area: Medical/Surgical - Acute Rehab

Houston Methodist Registered Nurse May 2014 - July 2016 (2 years 3 months)

Medical/Surgical – Stroke/Neurology

Village at Glennloch Farms
Registered Nurse
February 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 7 months)

St. Luke's Episcopal Hospital Registered Nurse July 2013 - March 2014 (9 months)

Medical/Surgical (Telemetry) - Open Heart Surgery Recovery

Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Master's Degree, MSN - Nursing Administration and Leadership · (2017)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2012 - 2013)